[{
    "question": "What are the final words of Jesus recorded in the New Testament",
    "answer": "Surely I come quickly"
}, {
    "question": "What is the name of the place where Jacob slept and dreamed of Jacob’s Ladder",
    "answer": "Bethel"
}, {
    "question": "Who told Naaman to wash in the river Jordan seven times in order to cure his leprosy",
    "answer": "Elisha"
}, {
    "question": "God tested Abraham by telling him to offer his only son as a burnt offering. Who was that son",
    "answer": "Isaac"
}, {
    "question": "How much was Judas paid to betray Jesus",
    "answer": "30 pieces of silver"
}, {
    "question": "Who witnessed Elijah being taken up to Heaven",
    "answer": "Elisha"
}, {
    "question": "Who hid Joshua’s spies from Jericho’s king",
    "answer": "Rahab"
}, {
    "question": "When they heard of the adversity that had befallen Job, how many of his friends came to comfort him",
    "answer": "Three"
}, {
    "question": "Who was the father of John the Baptist",
    "answer": "Zacharias"
}, {
    "question": "Who was the king of Israel when David slew Goliath",
    "answer": "Saul"
}, {
    "question": "Who said, Silver and Gold have I none, but such as I have I give thee",
    "answer": "Peter"
}, {
    "question": "How old was Abraham when his son Isaac was born",
    "answer": "100 years"
}, {
    "question": "Who took his rod and stretched out his hand upon the waters of Egypt to turn them into blood",
    "answer": "Aaron"
}, {
    "question": "When Jesus struggled with his cross, who was forced to bear it for him",
    "answer": "Simon from Cyrene"
}, {
    "question": "Psalm 119 is the longest chapter in the Bible. What is the shortest",
    "answer": "Psalm 117"
}, {
    "question": "At Christ’s crucifixion when did darkness come over the whole land and how long did it last",
    "answer": "Noon for three hours"
}, {
    "question": "How old was Gideon when he died",
    "answer": "A good old age"
}, {
    "question": "Who was the father of David?",
    "answer": "Jesse"
}, {
    "question": "To what land did Moses flee after killing the Egyptian soldier",
    "answer": "Midian"
}, {
    "question": "Christ’s first miracle was turning water into wine. Where did this occur",
    "answer": "The wedding at Cana"
}, {
    "question": "The first two disciples selected by Jesus were brothers. Name them",
    "answer": "Simon and Andrew"
}, {
    "question": "Who ate honey out of a lion’s carcass",
    "answer": "Samson"
}, {
    "question": "What famous city did Nebuchadnezzar rule",
    "answer": "Babylon"
}, {
    "question": "How many books of the Bible are named after women",
    "answer": "two – Ruth and Esther"
}, {
    "question": "Who is the only woman whose age is mentioned in the Bible",
    "answer": "Sarah"
}, {
    "question": "What is the name of the sea where Christ calmed a raging storm",
    "answer": "Sea of Galilee"
}, {
    "question": "What does 'Golgotha' mean",
    "answer": "The place of the skull"
}, {
    "question": "On the seventh day, how many times did Joshua’s army march around Jericho before the walls fell",
    "answer": "Seven"
}, {
    "question": "Whose flock was Moses tending when he encountered the burning bush",
    "answer": "Jethro"
}, {
    "question": "How long was Jonah in the belly of the great fish",
    "answer": "Three days and three nights"
}, {
    "question": "How old was Noah when the flood was upon the earth",
    "answer": "600 years"
}, {
    "question": "Which of Joseph’s (coat of many colors) eleven brothers said to not kill Joseph but to cast him in a pit instead",
    "answer": "Reuben"
}, {
    "question": "After his epiphany on the road to Damascus, how long was Saul without sight",
    "answer": "Three days"
}, {
    "question": "According to Paul in Romans, how many righteous people are there",
    "answer": "None"
}, {
    "question": "Adam and Eve had three sons. Cain was the firstborn followed by Abel. Who was the third son",
    "answer": "Seth"
}, {
    "question": "To whom did Jesus say, 'Man shall not live by bread alone.'",
    "answer": "Satan"
}, {
    "question": "How long had Lazarus been dead before being risen by Jesus",
    "answer": "4 days"
}, {
    "question": "For refusing to worship a false god, Shadrach, Meshach, and Abednego were cast into a fiery furnace by King Nebuchadnezzar. How much hotter than normal did the king order the furnace fire to be",
    "answer": "Seven Times"
}, {
    "question": "Which city was Jesus entering when Zacchaeus climbed a sycamore tree to see him",
    "answer": "Jericho"
}, {
    "question": "Which two wicked cities were destroyed by God in Genesis",
    "answer": "Sodom and Gomorrah"
}, {
    "question": "What kind of wood was used to make Noah’s Ark",
    "answer": "Gopher wood"
}, {
    "question": "How long was Daniel in the den of the lions",
    "answer": "One night"
}, {
    "question": "How tall was Goliath, the Philistine giant slain by David with a stone hurled from a sling",
    "answer": "Six cubits and a span"
}, {
    "question": "What animal is mentioned most frequently in both the New and Old Testaments",
    "answer": "The Sheep"
}, {
    "question": "Who wore the coat of many colors",
    "answer": "Joseph"
}, {
    "question": "According to the Bible, what weapons was the Philistine giant, Goliath carrying when he was slain by David",
    "answer": "A sword and a spear"
}, {
    "question": "What is the longest name in the Bible",
    "answer": "Mahershalalbashbaz"
}, {
    "question": "How many times did Peter deny Jesus",
    "answer": "Three"
}, {
    "question": "In Exodus, who was Miriam",
    "answer": "The sister of Aaron and Moses"
}, {
    "question": "What kind of tree did Zacchaeus climb to see Jesus enter Jericho",
    "answer": "Sycamore"
}, {
    "question": "Who was able to decipher Nebuchadnezzar’s dreams",
    "answer": "Daniel"
}, {
    "question": "Who was Joseph’s master in Egypt as stated in Genesis 37:36",
    "answer": "Potiphar"
}, {
    "question": "What was the last plague on Egypt",
    "answer": "The death of the firstborn"
}, {
    "question": "After he fled for his life, which tree did Elijah sleep under",
    "answer": "Juniper"
}, {
    "question": "Name David’s father.",
    "answer": "Jesse."
}, {
    "question": "What is the name of the second book in the Bible",
    "answer": "Exodus"
}, {
    "question": "The name of God is not mentioned in only one book of the Bible. Which one",
    "answer": "The Book of Esther"
}, {
    "question": "For what sum was Joseph sold by his brothers to the Ishmeelites",
    "answer": "20 pieces of silver"
}]
